http://tesla.liketelevision.com/liketelevision/legal/privacy.php?theme=guide

LikeTelevision.com - Privacy Policy
This statement discloses the privacy
practices and policy for the web site LikeTelevision.com. LikeTelevision™, Inc., the owner and operator of the web site, has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our
commitment to protecting your privacy.
The following
discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the web sites at www.LikeTelevision.com, and tesla.LikeTelevision.com. (also see
terms of use and disclaimer)
Information Collected
We use cookies to authenticate Members, to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password information so you don't
have to re-enter it every time you visit LikeTelevision's web site.
LikeTelevision uses Google AdSense to help us pay the bills, which helps us help you to watch stuff for free. As part of this insertion of ads, the LikeTelevision
sites use Google, as a third party vendor, to use cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users
based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (name and email) and demographic information
(city, state, zip code, country, age and gender).
We use customer contact information from the registration form to send our users information about new content and information about the company, rarely.
We have no interest in bugging you or being a pest. So, if we do send out something to our users, this might happen a few times a year.
We get annoyed by others who pester us, and we do our best to follow the Golden Rule, to do unto others, as we would like to be treated.
This site contains links to other sites; LikeTelevision.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
Message Boards
LikeTelevision™ makes use of message boards to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes
public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
LikeTelevision™
Inc., ATTN: William R. Krause, 19119 Brookgreen Garden Pl. Cornelius, NC 28031 or email: info@LikeTelevision.com
QUESTIONS? - info@liketelevision.com
